Guide to the Theodore Thornton Munger Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Sermons, 1858-(1880-1900) 1903; Series III; 3'9" (9 boxes)
  - Ecclesiastes: VII: 10, 1896 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Jonah I: 1,2, 1887 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Jonah I. 1,2, 1891 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Micah VI: 8, 1887 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Malachi III: 10, 1887 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - St. Matthew IV: 1, 1897 October 3 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - St. Matthew IV: 4, 1864 July (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - St. Matthew V:5, 1867 February (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - St. Matthew V: 7, 1882 October (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - St. Matthew V: 14-17, 1886 May 3 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - St. Matthew V: 15, 1886 January (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - St. Matthew V: 43-48, 1859 January (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - St. Matthew VI: 13, 1878 March (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - St. Matthew VI: 14, 15, 1900 March 25 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - St. Matthew VI: 1-12, 1898 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - St. Matthew VI: 22, 23, 1878 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - St. Matthew VI: 28, 1890 November 2 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - St. Matthew VII: 13-14, Undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - St. Matthew IX: 2, 1864 September (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - St. Matthew IX: 5, 1888 March 25 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - St. Matthew X: 29-31, 1864 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - St. Matthew XI: 11, 1881 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - St. Matthew XI: 16-20, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - St. Matthew XII: 18, 22, 1889 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - St. Matthew XII: 43-45, 1880 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - St. Matthew XII: 43-43, 1901 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - St. Matthew XII; 47, 1898 September 18 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - St. Matthew XIII: 3-9, 1890 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - St. Matthew XIII: 24-30, 37-43, 1880 April (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - St. Matthew XIII: 31, 32, 1886 January 10 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - St. Matthew XIII: 54-58, 1890 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - St. Matthew XIII: 31, 32, 1868 September (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - St. Matthew XIII: 51, 52, 1884 March 6 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - St. Matthew XIII: 51, 52 (no. 2) (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - St. Matthew XXII: 39, 1898 May 15 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - St. Matthew XXII: 42, 1890 October 5 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - St. Matthew XXIII: 28, 1865 December (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - St. Matthew XXIII: 37, 1896 November 1 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - St. Matthew XIV: 12, 1881 October (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - St. Matthew XV: 1-14, 1892 June 12 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - St. Matthew XVI: 6, 1888 November 11 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - St. Matthew XVI: 18, 1893 April 9 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - St. Matthew XVI: 20, 1860 July (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - St. Matthew XVIII: 7,8 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - St. Matthew XXVIII: 19, 1897 October 10 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - St. Matthew XXVIII: 20, 1867 January (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - St. Matthew XXIV: 2, 1872 November 17 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - St. Matthew XXV: 14-31, 1865 December (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - St. Matthew XXV: 29, 1899 October 15 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - St. Matthew XXV: 34-41, 1864 March (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - St. Matthew XXV: 36, 43, 1890 June 15 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - St. Matthew XXVI: 41, 1891 May 24 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - St. Matthew XXVI: 65, 66, 1862 December (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - St. Matthew XXVI: 75 & XXVII: 3-5, 1887 January 30 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - St. Matthew XXVI: 73, 1859 February (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - St. Matthew XXVI: 40, 1895 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - St. Matthew XXVII: 12, 1867 December (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - St. Mark I: 12, 13 & Proverbs I: 10, 1888 February 5 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - St. Mark II: 27, 1891 May 10 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - St. Mark II: 27, 28, 1895 sep 15 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - St. Mark IV: 19, 1873 April (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - St. Mark IV: 19, 1889 February 3 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - St. Mark IV: 28 & I Timothy I: 9, 1882 October (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - St. Mark X: 21, 1900 November (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - St. Luke I: 80, 1892 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - St. Luke II: 13, 14, 1888 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - St. Luke II: 14, 1880 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - St. Luke II: 34, 35, 1887 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - St. Luke II: 40, 1883 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - St. Luke III: 4-6, 1864 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - St. Luke IV: 16-19, 1863 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - St. Luke V: 18, 1887 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - St. Luke VI: 12, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - St. Luke VI: 49, 1890 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - St. Luke IX: 26, 1890 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - St. Luke IX: 28, 1889 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - St. Luke XI: 1 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - St. Luke XII: 1-3, 1893 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - St. Luke XII: 2 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - St. Luke XIII: 4, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - St. Luke XIII: 24, 1888 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - St. Luke XIII: 24 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - St. Luke XIV: 27, 1866 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - St. Luke XVI: 1-13, 1858 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - St. Luke XVI: 9, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - St. Luke XVI: 13, 1880 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - St. Luke XVI: 31, 1866 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - St. Luke XVII: 20-21, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - St. Luke XVIII: 10-15, 1854 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - St. Luke XVIII: 17, 1860 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - St. Luke XIX: 5, 1873 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - St. Luke XIX: 39, 40, 1883 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - St. Luke XIX: 12, 13, 1873 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - St. Luke XXI: 19, 1893 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - St. Luke XXIII: 46, 1890 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - St. Luke XXII: 3, 1888 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - St. Luke XXII: 42, 1891 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - St. Luke XXII: 61, 62, 1859 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - St. Luke XXIII: 33, undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - St. Luke XXIII: 34, 1887 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - St. John I: 9, 1862 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - St. John I: 47-51, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - St. John II: 5, undated (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - St. John III: 3, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - St. John III: 5, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - St. John III: 11, 12, undated (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - St. John III: 14, 1898 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - St. John III: 36, 1869 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - St. John XIV: 2, 1888 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - St. John XIV: 16, 17, 1892 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - St. John XIV: 19, 1858 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - St. John XXIV: 13, 14, undated (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - St. John IV: 6,7, 1886 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - St. John IV: 35, 1886 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - St. John IV: 36-38, 1886 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - St. John IV: 38, 1900 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - St. John V: 8-12, 1859 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - St. John V: 19, 20, 1888 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - St. John VI: 12, 1884 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - St. John VI: 60, 1886 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - St. John VI: 47-57, 1893 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - St. John VII: 17, 1887 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - St. John VII: 12, 1887 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - St. John VIII: 34, 1887 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - St. John VIII: 11, 1899 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - St. John IX: 4, 1893 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - St. John X: 10, 1892 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - St. John XI: 16, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - St. John XI: 25, 1864 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - St. John XII: 12-13, 20-21, 1900 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - St. John XII: 35, 1873 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - St. John XIII: 3, 4, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - St. John XIII: 3, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - St. John XIV: 1,2, 1890 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - St. John XV: 11, 1869 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - St. John XV: 15, 1887 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - St. John XV: 16, 1890 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - St. John XVI: 19, 1900 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - St. John XVI: 13, 1899 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - St. John XVI: 8-13, 1887 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - St. John XVII: 4, 1894 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - St. John XVII: 21, 1892 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - St. John XVIII: 37, 1858 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - St. John XXI: 7, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - St. John XXI: 15, 17, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - St. John XIV: 13, 14, 1896 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Acts I: 6-8, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Acts I: 9-11, 1888 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Acts I: 14, 1887 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Acts V: 34-41, 1865 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Acts VII: 59, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Acts VIII: 36, 1888 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Acts IX: 1, 1867 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Acts IX: 11, 1866 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Acts X: 38, 1891 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Acts XVI: 27, 30, 31, 1867 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Acts XVII: 10, 11, 1869 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Acts XVII: 26, 1900 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Acts XIX: 9, 1893 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Acts XXIII: 2-4, 1892 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Acts XXIII: 24 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Acts XXVII: 22-24, 1869 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Acts XXVIII: 3, 1888 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Acts XXVIII: 30, 31, 1859 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Romans I: 15-19, 1890 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Romans I: 17, 1897 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Romans VIII: 16, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Romans VIII: 19-23, 1893 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Romans VIII: 20, 21, 1885 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Romans IX: 13, 1880 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Romans X: 6-8, 1892 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Romans: XI: 18 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Romans XII: 2, 1896 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Romans XII: 6-8, 1880 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Romans XII: 6-8, 1898 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Romans XII: 21, 1879 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Romans XIV: 19, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Romans XV: 1-8, 1866 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - I Corinthians I: 1, 1891 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - I Corinthians I: 27, 28, 1877 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - I Corinthians III: 9, 1888 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - I Corinthians III: 11, 1896 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - I Corinthians VII: 31, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - I Corinthians IX: 25 27, 1881 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - I Corinthians IX: 25, 1892 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - I Corinthians XII: 4, 1886 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - I Corinthians XII: 4, 1867 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - I Corinthians XII: 28, 1867 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - I Corinthians XII: 13, 1899 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - I Corinthians XIII: 1-8, 1884 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - I Corinthians XIV: 1,2, 1895 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - I Corinthians XV: 10, 1892 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - I Corinthians XV: 19, 1886 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - I Corinthians XV: 41, 1868 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - I Corinthians XV: 41, 1891 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - I Corinthians XV: 19, 44, 46, 50, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - I Corinthians XV: 20, 1888 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - I Corinthians XV: 58, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - I Corinthians XV: 58, 1865 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - I Corinthians XVI: 13, 1898 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - I Corinthians XVI: 13, 1864 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - I Corinthians XVI: 13, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - II Corinthians III: 1,2, 1865 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - II Corinthians III: 6, 1900 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - II Corinthians V: 17, 1891 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Galatians I: 15-17, 1891 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Galatians II: 20, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Galatians VI: 10, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Galatians VI: 10, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Ephesians I: 22, 23, 1894 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Ephesians II: 6, 1882 September (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Ephesians III: 16, 1899 September 17 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Ephesians III: 17-19, 1888 September 2 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Ephesians VI: 4, 1889 September 29 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Ephesians VI: 10-18, 1890 September 21 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Philippians IV: 3, 1879 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Philippians IV: 8, 1898, 1904 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Philippians IV: 8, 1893 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Philippians IV: 11 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Colossians III: 16, 1898 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - "Extract from a Sermon Commemorative of Rev. Dr. Bushnell", 1876 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - "A Tribute to Bryant", 1878 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - "Sunday and the Railroads" (copy and portion of original), 1881 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - "The Post-Resurrection Journey to Galilee", 1890 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - I Thessalonians V: 14-24, 1901 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - I Thessalonians V: 19, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - I Timothy III: 15, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - I Timothy III: 15, 1891 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - I Timothy III: 16, 1890 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - I Timothy IV: 4, 1900 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - II Timothy I: 5, 1886 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - II Timothy II: 3, 1888 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - II Timothy III: 1-5, 1883 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - II Timothy III: 10, 1888 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Titus II: 11-13, 1869 (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Titus II: 11, 12, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Hebrews III: 12, 1867 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Hebrews VI: 19, 1889 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Hebrews VI: 19, 20, 1889 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Hebrews XI: 25 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Hebrews XI: 24, 25, 1881 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Hebrews XI: 37, 1886 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Hebrews:XI: 33-34 & Colossians III: 3, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Hebrews XI; 32-34, 1885 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Hebrews XII: 14, 1888 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Hebrews XIII: 10, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - St. James I: 2-4, 1889 (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - St. James I: 2 & St. Mark XIV: 38, 1885 (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - II Peter I: 5-8, 1886 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - II Peter I: 10, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - II Peter I: 5, 1888 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - II Peter III: 18 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - I John I: 8.9, 1890 (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - I John III: 2, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - I John III: 20, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - I John II: 5, 1869 (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - Revelation I: 6 & V: 10, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Revelations I: 6, 1864 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Revelation II and III, 1889 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Revelation IV: 11 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Revelation XXI: 5, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Revelation XXI: 16 & St. Matthew XIII: 33, 1897 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Revelation XI: 16, 17, 1900 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Revelation XXI: 13, 1885 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Revelation XXI: 16, 18, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Philip Brooks, memorial on, 1873 (Box 22, Folder 104)
  - "Christus Consolator" Part I (series of 10 sermons), 1885-1890 (Box 22, Folder 105)
  - "Christus Consolator" Part II, 1892-1894 (Box 22, Folder 106)
  - Part III, 1895-1900 (Box 22, Folder 107)
  - Fragments (Box 22, Folder 108-109)
  - Immortality, 1897 (Box 22, Folder 110)
  - Installation of Rev. H.E. Peabody, 1896 (Box 22, Folder 111)
  - Justice and Law, undated (Box 22, Folder 112)
  - The Municipal Church (newspaper account of), 1914 (Box 22, Folder 113)
  - The Pending International Arbitration Treaty, 1897 (Box 22, Folder 114)
  - Seventy-fifth Anniversary of North Adams Church, 1902 (Box 22, Folder 115)
  - Statement of Belief, Installation Sermon, United Church, New Haven, 1885 (Box 22, Folder 116)
  - Sunday and the Railroad, 1881 (Box 22, Folder 117)
  - "A Sermon, Introducer to the Pastorate over the Centre Church, Haverhill, Mass", 1864 (Box 22, Folder 118)
  - "Charge to Ernest Hume on his Ordination to the Ministry and Missionary Service", 1905 May 24 (Box 22, Folder 119)
  - "Charge to the People" given at the ordination of Frank K. [Lackey?], 1888 May 17 (Box 22, Folder 120)
- Special Files, 1806-(1880-1910) 1947; Series IV; 0.75; (2 boxes)
  SPECIAL FILES is divided into a "General" section, containing miscellaneous materials pertaining to various members of the Munger and Selden families, and a section devoted to Theodore Thornton Munger. The latter section contains mostly newspaper clippings and printed matter, much of it biographical in nature. There is also a folder of college notes and essays, including Munger's notes on the lectures of Professor Gibbs of Yale, a folder of materials, both manuscript and printed, related to the Robert Hume controversy, and a folder of reviews of Benjamin W. Bacon's biography of Munger.
  The series is arranged alphabetically by subject category.
  - General Special Files
    - Addresses: Ebenezer Munger, 1819, 1820 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Bills and Receipts of James H. Duncan, 1864 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Catalogue of the Officers and Students of Yale College, 1813 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Geography book of Cynthia Selden, 1806 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Photos, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Poems: by Mr. Bliss, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - by Mary Butts, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Sermon: "Turn Us Again, O God..." by David Selden, 1824 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Tributes and obituaries -- Munger Family, 1886, 1925-1929 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Tributes and obituaries -- Selden Family, 1877, 1905, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - T.T. Munger Special Files
    General note
    TRANSFERRED TO FOLIO
    - Biographical material; general, 1883, 1885, 1895, 1901-1908 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Biographical material; Reminiscences of classmate, 1851 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Biographical material; "Theodore Thornton Munger; An Early Liberal," by Frederick T. Persons, [1947] (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Biographical material; tributes, unveiling of memorial at the United Church, New Haven, 1911-1914 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Biographical material; tributes of friends and parishoners, 1910-1914 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Biographical material; tributes and obituaries, 1910 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - 1910 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Book lists, 1841, 1845, 1848 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Certificate of Membership, Western Reserve College, 1846 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - College notes and papers, 1849-1855 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Congregational Church, North Adams, Mass., Installation (newspaper clippings), 1877 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Congregational Church, United Church, New Haven, Installation, 1885 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Robert Hume Controversy, 1886, 1887, 1889, 1905, 1906, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Installation Paper of Rev. Evarts Wilson Pond (about Munger), 1922 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Latin fragment (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Notes on lectures by Prof. Gibbs, 1852 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Parish book, 1884 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Resignation from United Church, New Haven (printed material), 1901 May 1 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Manuscript of resignation from United Church, New Haven, 1900 October 7 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Reviews: The Life of T.T. Munger by Benjamin W. Bacon (printed and manuscript), 1914 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Sermon notebook: notes taken by Munger on sermons he heard while a student at Yale, 1850-1853 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - United Church, New Haven. Annual reports, 1888, 1890-1900 (Box 24, Folder 30-34)
- Folio
  This material is in CF36.
  - Diploma for the degree of Doctor of Divinity, Illinois College, 1883 (Box 25)
  - Diploma for the degree of Doctor of Sacred Theology, Harvard University, 1904 (Box 25)
  - Certificate of membership, Western Reserve College, 1846 (Box 25)